<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Experiences on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:50993/experience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Experiences on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:50993/experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>staff technical program manager</title>
      <link>http://localhost:50993/experience/box/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:50993/experience/box/</guid>
      <description>Revamping Infrastructure: Pioneering Box.com&amp;rsquo;s Hardware Engineering Revolution At Box.com, my role as a Hardware Engineering TPM was pivotal in revolutionizing the company’s infrastructure to support its expansive cloud storage services. The narrative of my journey at Box intertwines the technical with strategic triumphs, showcasing a relentless pursuit of optimization and performance enhancement.&#xA;Centralizing Hardware Operations: My tenure began with a critical challenge: to streamline and centralize the hardware engineering operations. Under my leadership, we unified the management of over 30 hardware configurations servicing more than 50 distinct platforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>rally health</title>
      <link>http://localhost:50993/experience/rally_health/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:50993/experience/rally_health/</guid>
      <description>Transforming Healthcare at Rally Health: Leading Through Innovation and Resilience At Rally Health, my journey was marked by a series of transformative challenges, each designed to elevate our healthcare solutions to new heights. As I embarked on these endeavors, the complexity of our systems and the scale of our ambitions pushed me to innovate and adapt relentlessly.&#xA;Medicare Fitness Program: Leading the charge on the Medicare Fitness program, I was thrust into the vortex of healthcare innovation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>staff technical program manager</title>
      <link>http://localhost:50993/experience/king_games/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:50993/experience/king_games/</guid>
      <description>King Games Levels Up: Leading the Charge in Player Loyalty and Engagement At King Games, known for its hit title Candy Crush, I had the unique opportunity to spearhead the launch of the company&amp;rsquo;s inaugural loyalty program, an ambitious project aimed at enhancing player engagement and retention. My role involved directing the technical launch of the loyalty site, where I led an international team that encompassed expertise from various domains including Candy Crush operations, loyalty programs, UX/UI design, product management, and engineering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>staff technical program manager</title>
      <link>http://localhost:50993/experience/apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:50993/experience/apple/</guid>
      <description>Revolutionizing Data Management at Apple: Streamlining Sales and Enhancing Global Collaboration As a Program Manager at Apple, working within the worldwide sales unit, I navigated the complex challenges of master data management, significantly enhancing operational efficiencies and cross-functional collaboration. My tenure was marked by a strategic overhaul of sales processes and product management alignment, which not only expedited time-to-market by 20% but also bolstered sales efficiency by an impressive 15%. By deploying innovative data ingestion and management features, I was instrumental in refining the integration of sales strategies with cutting-edge technological enhancements.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
